{
    "subject": "resource/Licence_to_Kill",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:James_Bond_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Licence to Kill is James Bond films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6810594201087952,
            "question": "What type of film is Licence to Kill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6060904860496521,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Licence to Kill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5769701600074768,
            "question": "Is there a specific villain in the film Licence to Kill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5359066724777222,
            "question": "Who directed Licence to Kill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5133869051933289,
            "question": "Is Licence to Kill part of a larger film series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47453051805496216,
            "question": "How does Licence to Kill compare to other films in its series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3874208331108093,
            "question": "What is the name of the series that includes Licence to Kill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3228170871734619,
            "question": "What is the main theme explored in Licence to Kill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2726265490055084,
            "question": "What is the overall tone of Licence to Kill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2486981898546219,
            "question": "What year was Licence to Kill released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Licence to Kill is James Bond films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6361_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall tone of Licence to Kill?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6361_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main theme explored in Licence to Kill?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6361_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the series that includes Licence to Kill?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6361_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6361_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that \"The subject of Licence to Kill is James Bond films,\" as they discuss various aspects related to the 1989 film, including its plot, cast, and place in the James Bond series."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}